you stop?
Shut it up!
This is my heart of the heart
and heart. We have their friends.
We're not there yet.
We don't have power to touch it.
We don't have power to reach out.
we're not even ready. We're not ready.
We're not ready.
I'm a complete genius,
I'm a complete genius.
Oh
Whoa!
That one hurt!
It's so cold!
Thanks to the help of Gardenfall, the
god atop the clouds, we descended safely.
The north is closer!
The south is!
You want to pull to the face?
You need to knock your
brain around in a wet run!
That's enough of you, too.
Do you ever stop squabbling? Knock it off.
Now that's easy.
Our new goal will be the last
island on the Grand Line.
However, we will require copies of all
four road poneglyphs to find its location.
You mean like the one we already found?
There is one in the land of Wano.
Yeah, our Mokumo Dukedom has one as well.
All this time, you guys
had stones back at home!
It's different than the last one more.
It's colored red.
But that's the kind I need most!
You should have told me sooner!
Let's get him, then two more to go.
Well, took a little effort, but I
nabbed a rubbing of linl and stones,
so with your help, I'll have three.
And I have a pretty good
hunch where the fourth one is.
Nice work, Roger.
We're even closer than I realized.
Our goal is right within our grasp.
Sorry to bring the mood down.
But I think that fall
really messed up our ship.
How is it?
It's hard to tell with my untrained eye.
But we're gonna need
some repairs and quick.
All right, then I know just where to go.
And where's that?
Water 7, the city of water.
And a quarter town.
Sounds romantic!
Full speed ahead! Let's go!
Thus, we ventured to a city of shipwrights
in order to repair the damages
to Roger's beloved vassal.
Roger, what brings you here today?
Greetings, Tom.
Hey, it's good to see you.
Tom, hey.
Wow, this is quite the reunion, isn't it?
Yeah, we missed you, friend.
Finished that project yet?
You talking about the Sea Train?
You're crazy.
That thing's still in the design phase.
You're still rowdy after
all this time, I see.
You must be an orphan, huh?
I can put in a good word
with our captain for you.
You guys are pirates, right? What of it?
Then no thanks, mister.
A bunch of pirates just
dumped me off here.
Did they now?
Never mind then.
Off we go!
This is Fishman Island.
I've been here with White Kitchen.
Best not to drop your guard, everyone.
It's no less deadly
the second time around.
Hey, Rayleigh.
Did you hear someone's feet just now?
You hearing voices?
There's no one all the way down here. No.
I heard it too.
Glad I'm not alone, Odin.
But who could be calling out
to us 10,000 leagues deep?
See, Toki?
That's Fishman Island.
How remarkable.
An entire city encased in a giant bubble.
Oh, look.
Fishman soldiers?
We're surrounded.
State your business, service
dwellers. Huh? Whoa, there.
No need to blow the man down.
Don't you recognize me, Neptune?
It's me, Roger.
Roger?
Ah, yes, I see now.
So you're the foretold ones.
I assure you, we're not
up to anything crooked.
A man of your stature's
scared of a little prophecy.
You're better than that.
It had cautioned us that very soon,
someone will destroy the
gates of Fishman Island.
Then suddenly you arrived,
so I'm a bit weary, you see.
Oh!
King Neptune!
It's been shattered!
The Sea Kings are chewing up the gate!
They're too gentle to do such a thing!
It can't be!
It came true.
There's a hole in the outer bubble!
Go and seal it up this instant!
So the prophecy was real.
And you nearly killed us over it!
The Sea Kings are in a restless state.
They're waiting for the
mermaid princess to be born.
Princess?
That means there's another prophecy.
So, the king should expect a baby?
How wonderful.
Wait a moment.
I can't have a child
before I've chosen a bride.
And it's far too soon.
I only took up the
throne a few months ago.
I'd trust the prophet, my lord.
She foresaw the death of
the former king exactly.
Her track record is solid.
And she was right about that beautiful...
Sorry, I mean that dreadful...
mermaid Otohime and her
political protest as well.
Certainly ill tidings, that one.
Those prophecies have been riling
up our entire kingdom as of late.
While that's interesting,
we didn't come down here to
catch up on small talk, Neptune.
Oh, I nearly forgot.
How's the progress?
Well, I presume two stones would
provide us with a clearer picture.
But it seems to be quite the opposite.
This is an apology from
someone named Joy Boy.
Incredible.
This man can really
transcribe them? Oh, yes.
Have you heard of a weapon
that controls the Sea Kings?
A weapon, you say?
The Stone on the Sky Island said
this is where it would be located.
An ancient weapon with the name of a god.
Poseidon, it's called.
Well, truthfully, that does
line up with Charlie's prophecy.
Though the implications of
it are rather chilling, hmm?
Every few centuries, a mermaid who
can speak to sea kings is born here,
and Charlie said one is coming soon.
I fear that she will be my daughter.
Hard to believe your soon-to-be little girl
is a weapon that can destroy the world.
I'm telling myself it's just a prediction.
And obviously a deadly weapon is
only deadly if you use it as such.
Who could have guessed that
Poseidon would be a mermaid?
So, Charlie, when will this
mermaid princess be born?
This many! Huh?
Seems we still have a decade.
Though I must ask, why would you
take an interest in such a weapon?
I'm disappointed in you!
You're wrong, Neptune.
We're not after the weapon.
The people who left the treasure behind
were the ones who called it that.
I promise we're just after their riches.
Are you feeling better?
Rest assured, old friend,
we will not be coming back in the future
to kidnap your hairy fish daughter.
Oh, she won't be hairy.
Gather up all of the crew.
It's time to ship up Ace's crew.
Wave goodbye but don't you cry.
Our memories remain.
Our days are not a passing dream.
Neverlasting though they seem to be.
So who will be today?
Yet the winds are lullaby.
Yo-ho-ho-ho.
Hey, me hearty-ups!
Good show!
Oded! Hey!
Something wrong, Red Dorry?
I think Lady Toki is sick! Where is she?
Toki, don't you worry.
I am right here with you.
What my advice?
Toki's traveled the world with you, but
there's something that should be considered.
Her original destination was Wano.
I'm a bit concerned for her well-being.
She's been at sea for a long time.
Her fatigue is catching up with her.
I'll give it to you straight.
If she presses on, she'll die.
She ought to disembark
at Wano. Don't risk it.
Toki is quite unwell.
Kin'emon and the others don't know
about Toki or your children yet.
So Dogstorm and I will be
happy to accompany her.
They'll want a familiar
face or two around.
It takes time to adjust to a new home.
We'll take good care of them.
I don't want you, Gar, to worry.
I will stay, too.
Toki?
I've forbid it.
You must go.
Stop being foolish.
You're not the type of man
who would give up halfway.
Do it.
You must go on or face divorce!
These rags are not ours by choice.
We have eagerly been waiting for your
return as we have unfortunate news.
I know you left Kuri in our hands, and we
do apologize as we have tried our best.
However, something wicked
has taken over Wano.
One moment.
You care for Odin, right?
Then I must implore you to stop.
Please, I beg of you.
Let him go.
Forgive me.
I am leaving again, at least for a time.
Even as I turned my back
on the land of Warnall,
I could tell something
about my home was amiss.
If I had stayed but a moment longer,
I knew I would never return to sea.
How could you do this, Lord Odin?
You damn jackass!
I quickly took a copy of
my country's Poneglyph and
hurried back to Roger's ship
before I could learn more.
It was my first time home in four
years, and I only stayed mere hours.
Jackass, indeed.
Then read the cliffs yourself
if you feel that way!
Apologies, Odin. Thank you.
We then headed to Cat Viper and
Dogstorm's homeland, the Mokomo Dukedum.
A country that's carried
on the back of an elephant.
Hope this works.
They say you can only find Zoe
with the help of a beaver card.
You're right.
It's not an island, but a large Pachydon.
Who is speaking to me?
Whose voice is this?
Hey, Odin, is there
something bothering you?
Sorry.
It's nothing really.
Just a strange feeling.
We have received a letter
from Dogstorm and Catviper.
They survived, did they?
I assumed the worst.
It was quite the fuss when
those naughty boys went missing.
Thank you, Karoo, for
relaying this message.
There's an uneasy feeling in the air.
It's not like you to worry.
It must be something bad.
I can sense it, too.
You too, Captain Roger?
It feels as if there's some enormous
presence and it's watching our every move.
There it is!
We found the last road, Poneglyph!
The Kozuki clan crashed!
The mink tribe are our
brethren, after all.
Just as the stories say.
Please!
I want to go!
I beg you, Karoo!
Hey, kiddo, you still
have some growing to do.
But don't worry.
You'll get your chance.
Just gotta wait your turn, huh?
What does that mean?
When the time comes,
I want you to help me.
Promise I will.
I'll be waiting for you, Karoo.
Take care of yourself, Pedro.
Over the course of our journey,
we acquired several real pwned
lifts and all four road pwned lifts.
The end of our adventure
was drawing ever closer.
Captain, are you okay?
Have you boys figured out
where we're headed yet?
Yeah, good to go.
How soon should we set out?
Immediately, of course. Yeah!
Let's go!
Whether it was good fortune or bad,
the apprentice Buggyiro suddenly
came down with a high fever.
He had to stay behind and forego
the final step of the voyage.
Don't have what it takes to make
it to the end of the trip, huh?
What a shame.
FUTURE!
I told you I'm feeling better now!
You're burning up so
much your face is red.
Just relax and sleep.
My nose is red again! I dare you!
I said your face!
Attaboy!
That's the spirit!
Don't encourage those two. Come on.
All the treasure is waiting for me, Mouse!
Stop pushing yourself!
I refuse to stay here!
Please, sir!
He gotta take me with you!
Just give it up already.
You need sleep.
Despite them always being
at each other's throats,
Red Taro took it upon
himself to look after him.
Honestly, it's hard to tell if
they're friends or enemies at times.
Please let me go with you.
I'm fine.
Well, we know how Buggy Giri feels.
What's your opinion on it?
You're all right with staying.
Odin?
Captain?
We'll make it out there one day, but
when we do, it should be on our own ship.
Thank
you.
It says the Roger Pirates finally did it!
They just made history!
That's the first time a crew traveled
all the way around the globe!
He's conquered it all!
The beginning to end!
Goal Roger!
King of the Sea!
And the King of the Pirates!
And on the day we reached that island, we
uncovered the entire truth of the world.
We learned of the 100 year void.
We learned of the people of the
D and of the ancient weapons.
Tales from a time when the land
of Wano was open to the world.
And in the face of the treasure,
there was one thing I remember most.
All I could hear was Roger.
He just laughed.
So did we all.
On and on until tears fell from our eyes.
Oh, Joy Boy.
Amazing.
I wish that I could have
lived in the same era as you.
This is quite the treasure
you left behind for me.
An incredible tale full of laughs.
Hey, everyone!
I was thinking, we're the first people
to step foot on this island in 800 years.
I think we should name it.
Love Tales!